A Finding Aid to the Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner Papers, circa 1914-1984, bulk 1942-1984, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Lee Krasner Papers, circa 1927-1984; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 8.6 Linear feet Box 7-15, 17
  - Audio and Video Recordings, circa 1964-1983; 2.10; Archival Resource Key
    - Lee Krasner Appearance on the 6PM News, 1973 November; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sarah Faunce Interview of Lee Krasner, 1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Lee Krasner lecture at Queens College, 1977 May 23; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Lee Krasner lecture at the Susanne Hilberry Gallery, 1977 November 21; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette
    - WQXR Radio Interview of Lee Krasner, 1980; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified Interview with Lee Krasner, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Poor sound quality at first; improves around 36 min. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified radio interview with Lee Krasner, Robert Indiana, and Paul Jenkins, 1976; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "Pollock a Beaubourg", 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic); 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 15, Folder 18-19)
    - John Gruen Interview of Lee Krasner, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound discs (lacquer); (See also Box 15, F9) (Box 17)